backyardgardener.com 2016-05-17

# Privacy Policy - Backyardgardener, Llc

Privacy Policy Statement  
This is the web site of Backyardgardener, LLC.

Our postal address is   
1825 56TH ST NE  
Tacoma, WA 98422

We can be reached via e-mail at [support[at]backyardgardener.com](mailto:support@backyardgardener.com)

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, no information on consumers who browse our Web page.

The information we collect is: .

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads and to support affiliate sales if a product was introduced by our domain.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by visiting us at [http://backyardgardener.com/contact.html](http://backyardgardener.com/).

We don't make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services they think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by or understanding.... We don't sell or give out any data or emails, unless you request a catalog..

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.  For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.  If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.  If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them if you are a subscriber to our forums.

Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, unique identifiers.

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

 **Children:** We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and feel strongly about protecting the rights and privacy of children. As such, we do not collect or use any personal information from children we know to be under the age of 13, and will remove personally identifying information about such minors from our system. We are compliant with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998. See this page for more information: [http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/coppa.htm](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/coppa.htm)

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at [http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm](http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm) or We are here to help.  Honestly, it's a simple website managed by one person..
